Dimitri Kvachakhia

Web Developer

I am a passionate, CMS developer. I have 2+ years of experience in developing web development, small and complex.... I have worked on a multitude of web and print-based projects for a range of clients providing Web Design (Photoshop) and Development (PHP, Laravel, HTML, CSS, SASS, JS, jQuery, WordPress, WooCommerce, Bootstrap, Responsive Layouts)...



info@dima.ge 🔀

571144078

Buachidze 10, Tbilisi, Georgia 👂

10 June, 2000 🎹

dima.ge 📾

linkedin.com/in/qvachakhia in

+995571144078

github.com/kvachakhia

EDUCATION

ProgrammingIT Step Academy

07/2018 – Present Courses

Programming

Tbilisi,Georgia

WORK EXPERIENCE

WordPress Developer

ImaxGropup

03/2019 - 06/2019

Tbilisi,Georgia

Junior WordPress Developer Webintelligence

07/2019 – 01/2020

Tbilisi

WordPress Developer Academy Of Digital Industries

SKILLS

Bootstrap

wordPress Themes Development			
WordPress Paid Theme development			0

Uikit • • • •

PHP

Laravel

Python / Django

React JS

Git O

Drupal O

Adobe Photoshop O

LANGUAGE

Georgian			
English		0	0
Russian		0	0

INTEREST

Programming

Back-end Development